{
  "surveys":[
      {"id":1,"name":"NPS","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answers":["1 Not at all likely","2","3","4","5","6","7","8","9","10 Highly likley"]}]}
      },
      {"id":2,"name":"Employee Satisfaction","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answers":["Very unsatisfied","Unsatisied","Neutral","Satisfied","Very satisfied"]}]}
      },
      {"id":3,"name":"Lunch Order","content":{"questions":[
          {"question":"What would you like for lunch today?",
          "answers":["Pizza","Sandwiches","Sushi","Tacos"]}]}
      },
      {"id":4,"name":"Personal Questions","content":{"questions":[
          {"question":"What is your favorite color?",
          "answers":["Red","Blue","White","Black"]}]}
      }]
  ,
  "responses":[
      {"id":77747295293,
      "content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"6"}]
      },"completed":"2021-05-25T21:41:17.187Z"},
      {"id":707320912578,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T22:20:25.259Z"},
      {"id":753380922800,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Pizza"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T22:20:25.259Z"},
      {"id":647907540747,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"2"}]},"completed":"2022-02-07T22:39:40.442Z"},
      {"id":569893223806,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"6"}]},"completed":"2022-02-07T22:39:43.262Z"},
      {"id":84375635547,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley"}]},"completed":"2022-02-07T22:39:44.987Z"},
      {"id":569895396754,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley"}]},"completed":"2022-02-07T22:39:45.348Z"},
      {"id":246161667384,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"3"}]},"completed":"2022-02-07T22:39:49.492Z"},
      {"id":689792528033,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"3"}]},"completed":"2022-02-07T22:39:49.670Z"},
      {"id":317408188631,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"3"}]},"completed":"2022-02-07T22:39:49.829Z"},
      {"id":317408188632,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What is your favorite color?","answer":"Red"}]},"completed":"2022-03-07T22:39:49.829Z"},
      {"id":317408188633,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What is your favorite color?","answer":"Red"}]},"completed":"2022-03-08T22:39:49.829Z"},
      {"id":317408188634,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What is your favorite color?","answer":"Red"}]},"completed":"2022-03-09T22:39:49.829Z"},
      {"id":317408188635,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What is your favorite color?","answer":"Blue"}]},"completed":"2022-03-10T22:39:49.829Z"},
      {"id":317408188636,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What is your favorite color?","answer":"Black"}]},"completed":"2022-03-11T23:39:49.829Z"},
      {"id":317408188637,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-03-12T23:39:49.829Z"},
      {"id":317408188638,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Pizza"}]},"completed":"2022-03-13T23:39:49.829Z"}
  ]
}
